[Music]
kids go wash up
dinner is almost ready can I sit next to
you this year mom of course you can sue
you you don't have to ask that every
year likes in needy [ __ ] ha ha ha I'm
sitting next to Bartleby so make sure
there is a large bucket of potatoes at
the end of the table
[Music]
good afternoon everybody thanks for
inviting us over for dinner
it means so much to us please accept
this boat a tow solid it is an old
family recipe of mine it was created by
my great-grandfather and passed down
eventually to me it's really really good
it looks like he just crapped in a
bucket when he obviously cares so deeply
parade that's so funny you better not
let Robotnik here you're saying stuff
like that thing face shut up why did you
spank my butt so you think my potato
salad looks like poop
don't you let's see how you'll feel
about it when we get back home and I
make you eat it off my nipples calm down
your boy in sir it is potato salad eat
under there is not roti mint at
everybody we got a table at dinner
oh man I dropped my orange under the
couch I can't reach it
looks like somebody needs some
assistance need some help down there B
wait Bart Levy that's not an orange
that's my big ass butt cheek hey [ __ ]
you know how to see if a melon is ripe
young you just give it a good smack Oh
Oh daddy spank me again right on my butt
okay are you avoiding this no what
happened oh it's uh it's it's nothing I
see the gang is all here
don't worry Robotnik it's the holidays
nobody is holding any grudge against you
guys today it is a time of peace we are
coming together not as enemies but as
friends
okay I guess you're right
oh I didn't see you will arrive yeah
just in time for dinner we were getting
ready to eat
I helped mom with the green beans and
mashed potatoes how did I do mother oh
you did good very good I must say that I
am quite hungry after the ride here I
could go for some food right about now
of course you're hungry you fatty
fake oMG I bet he stopped by McDonald's
on the wheel yeah
shut your mouth [ __ ] where the hell do
you think you're talking to
they what is that thing that fell out of
his pocket that's the McDonald's wrapper
oh my God he actually did it what the
[ __ ] is de-sect are you up
wow what a fat [ __ ] why don't you go
back to McDonald's fat-ass look what you
did [ __ ] now the whole room is laughing
at me I'll [ __ ] kill you
no you won't do me man if you ever hair
ass my little girl again I will stick my
foot up your ass and kick you like a
soccer ball into the Sun now get into
the kitchen fatty it's dinnertime
okay everybody hold hands with those
next to you before we eat we're going to
give thanks don't be shy remember today
we're all family
[Music]
Manek would you like to have the honors
of starting us off you bet your ass I
would mama I'm thankful for making it
into the top 900 in fortnight I'm also
thankful to Uncle Chuck for filming me
doing the floss dance and taking me to
the rental store so I could rent
battlefield 5 for the weekend I'm
thankful for making it into the top 400
and for tonight you son of a [ __ ] you
can't just take my answer like that and
change it to make you look better than
me well I'm thankful for friends family
and the fact that nobody at the stable
is black I'm into that
what about you Sonic what are you
thankful for what am I thankful for well
I'm due see that's that's kind of a
loaded question
I don't believe in God but I guess if I
had to be thankful for something
I would be thankful for the most amazing
men in my life how about you Bart levy
cool I'm thankful for being rich Sleet
Goddamnit Dingo I don't even like you
why the hell you got to embarrass me in
front of everyone like this I'm thankful
for Frank Roberts the sexy guy who lives
a couple blocks down the street not only
has he given me some of the best sex
ever he's also my plastic surgeon just
last week he made my milk chug the whole
two cm bigger I had trouble
even finding a shirt this morning that I
could fit into I'm thankful that I was
born a man and not weak women the calls
men are the superior species men are
strong and wise while a woman's only
strength is that she can make a variety
of sandwich's for us men there is a
reason that men are the ones out there
in war the field of battle shedding
blood beneath waves of endless bullets
and death fighting for what they believe
in
men are strong and determined and they
get the job done and women well they
can't do [ __ ] God made men and his image
for a reason if anybody here disagrees
I dare you challenge me here and now
spoiler alert you won't win I see nobody
wants to challenge me I don't blame you
I know I'm right too men shouldn't be
fighting amongst each other when we can
put women down and in their place
instead raise your hand if you're
picking up what I'm putting down
it doesn't matter if you understand now
someday you will
you all will your men after all what the
BAL Probot Nick he still hasn't told us
about what is thankful for oh yeah
that's right go on big guy tell us what
you're thankful for you seem like a good
looking guy I bet you're thankful for
your ability to pick up [ __ ] ha ha
Wow you really mean that
to be honest I never really thought
about what I'm thankful for
I bet he's thankful for all the innocent
people that he killed in cold blood boy
I really expect us to forgive a you say
we'll bust our palate Levitch I bet he's
thankful for not giving us our paychecks
last week
ain't that right thing face you know if
any of you [ __ ] have anything to say
to me you could say it to my face
instead of whispering to each other like
a bunch of Muslims planning a terrorist
attack actually screw it you guys are
right I'm only thankful for one thing
and one thing only you want to know what
the fact that one thing is [ __ ] I'll
tell all of you
this guy I'm thankful for this fine
piece of ass got a problem with well
suck my sweaty balls this guy
single-handedly took over Mobius in a
single [ __ ] night and you [ __ ] you
want to know what the [ __ ] happened to
your paychecks I spend it all of it on
nothing but whitey-tighties and fruit
gushers can we just eat now I'm [ __ ]
starving mama I don't give a [ __ ]
everybody dig in there's more than
enough to go around well if nobody else
is going to bring this up I guess I'll
just be the one to ask are you two like
[ __ ] or what what the hell Sleet you
can't just ask people if they're gay
what's wrong with asking I'm genuinely
curious these two were literally having
butt sex behind the couch when we walk
in don't act like you didn't see that
[ __ ]
it's alright Robotnik I'll take it from
here I deal with these kinds of people
all the time to answer your question
Sleet yes me and Bart levy are in a
homosexual relationship we've been
together for years now and we love each
other very much is there a problem
because if so I could take you out back
and have my fists fix it for you oh no I
was just I was
just curious that's all I actually think
you two make a pretty cute couple Elena
Primera host what acai your rare you did
yourself this year the turkey is so
[ __ ] good I'm really glad you like it
Charles
Sonja helped me with it all morning
speak for yourselves to the rest of us
it looks smells and tastes like dried
[ __ ] I wouldn't show up it up - for a
million dollars and everybody here knows
I'll stick anything up - for the right
price
don't listen to that [ __ ] Elena you know
what it's talking about that'll kill
your mother is nice and through it who's
3ko miss wait Bobby's um Charles can you
let go of my hand
you're making me pretty uncomfortable
here no you want to stay look at this
for a little while along here it's not a
very very well yet all done sleek
eighties proceedures whoa your answer a
source of Elena take a host Ricky when
we were kids don't pull your wife from
match what the [ __ ] mama are you all
right you and Uncle Chuck aren't
fighting again are you you promised you
wouldn't
it's the holidays oh of course not Sonia
I just fell out of my chair that's all
we all know that's [ __ ]
if this Beach world who's Domingo what's
a story Carol here so old you know the
Dumpty
you
[Music]
hahaha
Manic what the [ __ ] is this the black
guy dancing with chicken meme is like 10
years old you are crazy
you're [ __ ] crazy bro but that's what
we all love about you you crazy son of a
[ __ ]
Yahoo no Elena face I study Nancy and
Gracie incest was perfectly okay what
the [ __ ] did a host get a text message
he even ever gotten a text message a you
wonder if it's from tech 17 general
cheeky Ravenstahl cannot the local
thrift store a which us what means that
size store [ __ ] ass always come here
when they went ye ever Jana get the [ __ ]
down
daddy is about togetic Ali from our
chick with before yes
[Music]
what is this this is no chip it's ghost
so maybe like million chicken in front
of arrival miss me with that face it
ahahahahahaha kids put your damn phones
away while we're at the table or I'm
gonna come over there and shove a
handful of Brussels sprouts up your
asses
so how are all of you guys enjoying my
potato salad is that what that is
damn I thought somebody took a big [ __ ]
in a bucket full of cheese you're right
Mindy hell I wouldn't even eat it if it
was smothered all over your boobs well
you do not be so rude to our guests sure
his potato salad smells like poop but
that doesn't give us the right to call
it out to him at the table no no you
know what if that's how you all feel
then I'll just make you eat it
open wide you damn dirty [ __ ]
oh no no I have potato salad all over my
big boobies don't worry baby
we can go up to my room after dinner and
I'll clean it off for you
with my own I'm sorry but I would like
to know what little man threw potato
salad on my plate no no don't all gasp
in unison I simply want to know who it
was come forward I wouldn't hurt you
that would be me [ __ ] you've got a
problem actually yes
now you have a problem with you and your
stinky potato salad I want you out of
this house No out of this neighborhood
within the next 5 min and if you're not
well let's just say that my foot will be
up your ass I suggest you get a move on
fat man the clock is ticking Happy
Thanksgiving
Sleet then go get your asses up we're
getting out of here before Bart lab'
kills me
[Music]
this Thanksgiving his ruined just like
every year every [ __ ] year all we've
done is fight can't we all just get
along without throwing punches for one
day out of the year we are acting like a
bunch of black people up in this [ __ ]
we are white we are supposed to be more
sophisticated Vanis you know what your
little app in which you're apparently
only embarrassing over fun if you know
what was good for yo yo worried to stage
before anyway others in front of IANS
Charles how many times did I have to
tell you not to lay a hand on my kid
don't make me call the police again
don't water which email in down totally
cold story yet in donkey spittle distant
opiate well some Thanksgiving this
turned out to be
come on Manic let's go play battlefield
five
my cute little bitch what's wrong you
look as though you're on the brink of
Tears
it's nothing Bart levy it's just this is
your first Thanksgiving with my family I
wanted it to be special
but of course my stupid family had to
embarrass themselves like hallways [ __ ]
you don't have to worry I'm having fun
just being here here's a cloth for your
tears I don't need it I'm not crying
Bart levy I mean it
I'm not some weak little boy who needs a
big strong man to protect them something
tells me that that isn't true
Oh Bart levy you're right I love you so
much this has been the best Thanksgiving
ever
you bet your sweet little as it has now
give daddy a kiss that sweeter than any
pumpkin pie
[Music]
you